<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Act 2 :: SANS Holiday Hack Challenge 2025</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/index.html</link>
    <description>Act 2 – Applied Analysis and Controlled Exploitation Act 2 shifts from observation to active analysis across multiple domains, including email infrastructure, web applications, identity systems, and network devices. The challenges require moving between tools, protocols, and abstractions while maintaining control over scope and intent. The difficulty increase is driven less by technical complexity and more by the need to correlate information across layers. This act reflects day-to-day defensive and offensive security work, where insight comes from stitching together partial truths rather than exploiting a single flaw in isolation.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/act2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Retro Recovery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/retro-recovery/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/retro-recovery/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Join Mark in the retro shop. Analyze his disk image for a blast from the retro past and recover some classic treasures. Mark DeVito mission statement I am an avid collector of things of the past. I love old technology. I love how it connects us to the past. Some remind me of my dad, who was an engineer on the Apollo 11 mission and helped develop the rendezvous and altimeter radar on the space craft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail Detective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/mail-detective/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/mail-detective/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Help Mo in City Hall solve a curly email caper and crack the IMAP case. What is the URL of the pastebin service the gnomes are using? Maurice Wilson mission statement Hey there! I’m Mo, on loan from the Air Force, and let me tell you - Counter Hack is the best job I have ever had!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idorable Bistro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/idorable-bistro/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/idorable-bistro/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Josh has a tasty IDOR treat for you—stop by Sasabune for a bite of vulnerability. What is the name of the gnome? Josh Wright mission statement I’m a teetotling hacker.&#xA;I sleep about 4 hours a night.&#xA;Photography is my hobby, but the anachronistic sort: before 1900.&#xA;Teaching people how to hack and protect systems is my passion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dosis Network Down</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/dosis-network-down/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/dosis-network-down/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Drop by JJ’s 24-7 for a network rescue and help restore the holiday cheer. What is the WiFi password found in the router’s config? Janusz Jasinski mission statement Hello! I’m JJ. I like rock, metal, and punk music. That’s all I have to say about that.&#xA;I accept BTC.&#xA;Skeletor is my hero&#xA;Alright then. Those bloody gnomes ‘ave proper messed about with the neighborhood’s wifi - changed the admin password, probably mucked up all the settings, the lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Gnome Identity Provider</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/rogue-gnome-identity-provider/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/rogue-gnome-identity-provider/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Hike over to Paul in the park for a gnomey authentication puzzle adventure. What malicious firmware image are the gnomes downloading? Paul Beckett mission statement Hey, I’m Paul!&#xA;I’ve been at Counter Hack since 2024 and loving every minute of it.&#xA;I’m a pentester who digs into web, API, and mobile apps, and I’m also a fan of Linux.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantognome Leap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/quantognome-leap/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/quantognome-leap/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Charlie in the hotel has quantum gnome mysteries waiting to be solved. What is the flag that you find? Charlie Goldner mission statement Hello! I’m not JJ. I like music.&#xA;I accept AI tokens.&#xA;I like quantum pancakes.&#xA;I enjoy social engineeering.&#xA;Check back with me later - I might have something for you to help with!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going in Reverse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/going-in-reverse/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/going-in-reverse/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Difficulty Description 2/5 Kevin in the Retro Store needs help rewinding tech and going in reverse. Extract the flag and enter it here. Kevin McFarland mission statement Hello, I’m Kevin (though past friends have referred to me as ‘Heavy K’). If you ever hear any one say that philosophy is a useless college degree, don’t believe them; it’s not. I’ve arrived where I am at because of it. It just made the path more interesting.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>