<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sans Holiday Hack Challenge 2025 - Introduction :: SANS Holiday Hack Challenge 2025</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Foreword The SANS Holiday Hack Challenge is often described as a game, but it is better understood as a guided walk through how security systems actually fail. Each objective is deliberately scoped, self-contained, and approachable, yet designed to surface the same patterns that appear in real environments: misplaced trust, misunderstood protocols, weak assumptions, and small decisions with outsized impact.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:28:44 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Act 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Act 1 – Foundations and Observation Act 1 focuses on establishing core mental models rather than exploiting edge cases. The challenges emphasize how systems communicate, how data moves across boundaries, and how small configuration details influence security outcomes. Difficulty remains low, but the act trains disciplined observation and protocol literacy rather than trial-and-error problem solving. This mirrors real-world security work where understanding normal behavior is a prerequisite for detecting abnormal or malicious activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Act 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Act 2 – Applied Analysis and Controlled Exploitation Act 2 shifts from observation to active analysis across multiple domains, including email infrastructure, web applications, identity systems, and network devices. The challenges require moving between tools, protocols, and abstractions while maintaining control over scope and intent. The difficulty increase is driven less by technical complexity and more by the need to correlate information across layers. This act reflects day-to-day defensive and offensive security work, where insight comes from stitching together partial truths rather than exploiting a single flaw in isolation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Act 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Act 3 – Integration, Depth, and Decision-Making Act 3 emphasizes depth, ambiguity, and integration of skills developed earlier. The challenges require comfort with uncertainty, careful reading of instructions, and deliberate sequencing of actions across hardware, software, and application layers. Mistakes are more costly, and brute force approaches are actively punished. This act aligns closely with real-world incidents and complex assessments, where success depends on restraint, planning, and understanding when not to act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endgame</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/endgame/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:59:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/endgame/index.html</guid>
      <description>Upon completion of the final objective, the game transitions to the endgame sequence at the Grand Hotel, where the full Counter Hack team is presented:&#xA;Interacting with Santa provides a consolidated narrative explanation of the events leading up to the incident and its resolution. Santa’s dialogue frames the outcome as the successful prevention of a sustained environmental manipulation attack against the Dosis Neighborhood. It also contextualizes Frosty’s actions as being driven by a persistent existential threat—seasonal melting—and highlights an unexploited alternative resolution that did not involve infrastructure sabotage or coercion through third parties (the Gnomes):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Roger Johnsen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:28:44 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</guid>
      <description>Roger Johnsen is an information security professional with a strong focus on Blue Team operations, threat hunting, and detection engineering. His work centers on strengthening SOC capabilities through hypothesis-driven hunting, analyst education, and the development of tooling and processes that scale beyond individual investigations.&#xA;Roger is an active participant in Capture The Flag (CTF) competitions, with particular emphasis on technically demanding, long-form challenges such as the SANS Holiday Hack Challenge and platforms like TryHackMe and Hack The Box. He approaches CTFs as controlled environments for validating techniques, stress-testing assumptions, and refining investigative workflows that directly translate into real-world security operations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>